{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "dsfg",
      "answers": [
        "asdf",
        "fg",
        "asdfsd",
        "fg"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sfsdaf",
      "answers": [
        "dsafasdf",
        "dsfgsdfgsdf",
        "sdfsadfas",
        "dsfgsdfgqwr"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sfsdaf",
      "answers": [
        "dsafasdf",
        "dsfgsdfgsdf",
        "sdfsadfas",
        "dsfgsdfgqwr"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "aasdf",
      "answers": [
        "afsd",
        "fdsadf",
        "sdf",
        "asdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "aasdf",
      "answers": [
        "afsd",
        "fdsadf",
        "sdf",
        "asdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "1",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "prompt": "asdf",
      "answers": [
        "fgsdf",
        "dfasdf",
        "dfgdsf",
        "dffads"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Poop",
      "answers": [
        "crap",
        "doo doo",
        "feces",
        "lasagna"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "3",
      "id": 13
    }
  ]
}